there once was a ship that
put to see the name of
the ship was a believe of
T the winds blew up my
bully boys blow me
bring my sugar
and tea and rum 1
day when the tongue is done
we'll take our leave and go
she had not been 2
weeks from Shore and down on
her all right whale bore the
captain called All Hands 1
day when the time is done
we'll take our leave and go
before the board
had hit the water the wheels
still came up and caught her
hands to the side and the
for her when she dived down
low soon me the
woman come sugar and
no Lane was
cut know will was free the
captain's mind was not of greed
and he belong to the wilman's
creature took that ship into
soon May the
Wella man come to bring us
sugar and tea and rum 1
day when it's on it is
done we'll take our leave and
go du du
du du du du du du
du du du for 40 days
or even more the lane when
slack and tape once more oh
both were lost there were only
4 but still that wielded
go soon lemon
come to bring us sugar and
tea and Mom 1 day when
it's coming is done we'll take
our leave and go as far
as Affairs the fight still on
the lanes not cut and the
wheels not gone the will of
man makes us regular cold to
encourage the Captain Crew and all
soon come to
bring us sugar and tea and
rum 1 day when it's
time it is done we'll take
our leave and go soon
me the well a man come
to bring us sugar and tea
and rum 1 day when the
time is done we'll take
our leave and go