creating custom chat Bots for your
website can be insanely powerful but if
you don't have any experience it could
be quite overwhelming so I'm going to
show you how to set up a b press chatbot
from scratch the variables and features
you can play with step by step even if
you never used it before so by the end
of this video you can have your own
custom chatbot on your website so you
can improve customer chats save money
and give a more personal touch on your
website if I search AI automation agency
into YouTube A lot of people are talking
about how to make chat Bots for other
people this guy made $112,000 a month in
42 days this one 2,500 a week this guy
sells it for $3,000 per chatbot this guy
makes $5,000 a month and you might be
wondering does it work yes because you
can build chatbots for other people that
does customer support lead generation
e-commerce assistant virtual assistant
language transl ation and information
retrieval and as far as I know if you
help a business do something easier
faster or better they are willing to pay
for that so I'm going to show you how to
make a few different chat Bots step by
step so you can create this for yourself
and your business or again you can sell
it to somebody else but before that drop
a comment down below AI automation
agency if you're interested in this
maybe I'll make more videos on it in the
future step number one go to bot press
as you can see build chat gbt chatbots
surprisingly fast this is from bot press
that is sponsoring this video which I'm
very happy for because they are the
current best chatbot Creator even
compared to custom chat gbts the answers
you get with this is way more reliable
so just click on get started it's free
now that you're on the inside let's
create your first chatbot all you need
to do is click on create chatbot right
here and then click on edit as you can
see you can learn bot press start from
scratch or AI public personality we're
going to start from scratch use the
template and this is how it looks
straight off the bat all we need to do
is just delete this node and we're going
to keep this simple node in here if you
never build a chatbot this tutorial is
for you I'm going to go from complete
Basics I'm even going to delete this one
so you can start from scratch as you can
see we start with a start node and we
have an end node all we need to do to
begin is right click click standard node
and now we are beginning I'm going to
drag the start note in here and let's
write for example now I'm going to go
over to the left side where you can see
all of these cards this is everything
that we can do within a node to still
keep it basic I'm going to drag a text
card right into our node as you can see
this prompts us to send a message I'm
going to write hello welcome to your
personalized chat bot and now what we
could do is drag from the node over to
the end and we would have a complete
chat bot that doesn't do anything but we
actually wanted to do a lot of things so
in this example let's imagine that I run
an AI agency that helps companies from
one to 100 employees set up their own
custom chat Bots first we're going to
ask them how many employees they have
then we're going to ask them if they
need more personalized help that gathers
their email and sends them to an
appointment scheduler this example will
help you set up any chat bot that you
want as we go through the different
filters and cards to add so we're not
going to drag this one to the end we're
going to right click and add a standard
card I'll drag the El card over to the
standard new card and I'm going to name
it ask now I'm going to use any of these
capture information cards to get a
prompted response in this case we're
going to use the number because what
we're going to ask is how many employees
does your company have we're then going
to click on select and create variable
so we can store their answer later I'm
going to call it num click on enter and
I'll show you how we're going to use
that later I'm going to click on ADD
card and we're going to add two
different expression nodes that triggers
on different different answers I'll
click on the number again and here we
can now start writing our choices I'm
going to say between 1 and 10 I'll click
on the plus icon and write above 11 use
natural language here because it
actually understands as you can see on
the Node itself we actually got two
outputs here now so I'm going to delete
these cuz we don't need them for the
next step I'm going to add a standard
node and I'm going to add other standard
node and now I'll teach you about the
variables if I add a card here and click
on text again what we can do is say
something like hey cool that your
company has we'll click on this variable
that will write exactly what they just
said then we'll say something like what
we recommend is watching this YouTube
video and it could be a landing page it
could be anything that you made for that
specific audience So This Is The Answer
between 1 and 10 and then we can just
copy this entire card and just paste it
in the second card it will have the
exact same number except you will just
change out the link or information for
that target audience make sure to
connect the nodes and our chat bot is
starting to look nice The Next Step
We'll add a new standard node and for
this one we'll add a card that is a
multiple choice with that selected we'll
go over to the right and add choices
like yes and no with the question would
you like to talk with one of our AI
experts we just make sure to connect the
nodes both of them into the same field
and now based on their answer you can
see no here you can see yes here for yes
we'll add a standard node that we're
going to add this email address card so
we can get their email I'll say okay
cool what is your email so we can
contact you I'll also create a new
variable called email and we'll also add
a standard node for the no and we'll
send a message that's more ending
sending them to our YouTube channel or
maybe your blog and we'll connect these
notes but since we're only making a
simple chatbot I want to show you some
more advanced features if you go to the
top and click on flows you can see that
you can add a default knowledge base
this is good for you because you can
have answers in here that the AI will be
able to answer we can just click on
knowledge based source and here you can
upload documents with web pages web
search or text document we can add pages
and add from sitap this is by far the
most extensive way to get your entire
website database into your chatbot take
for example this random website that I
found all you need to do is to go to the
end of the URL and then write
sitemap.xml and here we see all of their
data and you probably have this on your
website as well copy this link and now
you can see that they got
4,900 URLs that you can add the data
from this is important to you if you
have an FAQ about your shipping times or
return of items maybe refund policy your
chatbot can answer all of that just like
that we'll then plug everything into the
end all I'm going to do is Click publish
and then we can talk to it in the
emulator in the right I'm just going to
write it hello and just like that it's
writing to us hello welcome to your
personalized chat bot how many employees
does your your company have and it will
give us these different answers I'm
going to click on between 1 and 10 and
if you remember from our flow it's now
going to go through and say hey cool
that your comp this is the reason why we
test has between 1 and 10 what we
recommend is watching this video and
this is a personalized video for them
would you like to talk to one of our AI
experts so now we're going to click on
yes it's going to say okay cool what's
your email so we can contact you I'll
write my email and we captured the
variable email but we didn't actually
say anything else and that's what the
last step is for right click standard
text again that's something like thanks
for sending your email you can schedule
a call with our air expert on kendly
we'll also be reaching out to you
shortly via email we just connect it up
to each other and to the end and that's
when we reach the final step all you
need to do is click on flows and we have
a tab called conversation end this
basically trigger when we reach the end
point of the other workflow and we get
this Handler that can literally do
anything that we tell it to what's
popular is having multiple choices and
continue into different workflows but to
keep it simple we'll just say thank you
and goodbye just like this and then we
can publish your chatbot looks like this
it's acting exactly like before giving
the exact responses that we prompted it
to now to embed this bot press chatbot
on your website all you need to do is to
have a botpress cloud account you
probably do a botpress bot and you make
sure that you've published your Bot we
did all of that now we just go to the
integration Hub which looks like this
click on the web chat integration and
make sure that it's installed then you
can either use your sharable url that
shows the page that I just showed you or
what I like to do embed the script on
your website if you haven't done this
before just paste this code between the
body tags of of your HTML page you find
this by clicking on your Bot clicking on
Integrations going to the preconfigured
and here you have your script just copy
and paste it directly to your website
and just like that you have your own
custom AI chatbot on your website if you
need more help check out bot press's
YouTube channel that has over 200
tutorials on it or if you want to start
your chat bot now click the link in the
description to get started for free
thanks for watching the video and I'll
see you in next one peace